Tufts Weekly UP056
Tufts Archival Research Center
- Tufts Weekly, 1895 -- 1968; UP056.001; 2.4 Linear Feet; 62 Volumes; 19.78 Gigabytes; 2079 Digital Object(s)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1967 February 17; UP056.001.060.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 15 Megabytes (Box 60)
    Richard Alpert [A1952] Leads LSD movement with Timothy Leary [incl. photo].
  - Tufts Weekly, 1967 February 24; UP056.001.060.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 60)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1967 March 03; UP056.001.060.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 60)
    [Admissions] Undergraduate admissions: an overview. p. 3.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1967 March 10; UP056.001.060.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 60)
    Phillip A. Anderson [A1968] Concert Jazz Band Leader [incl. photo].
  - Tufts Weekly, 1967 March 17; UP056.001.060.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 60)
    Donald Altvater [A1967] student council representative in charge of Parents' weekend [includes photo]
  - Tufts Weekly, 1967 March 31; UP056.001.060.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 60)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1967 April 07; UP056.001.060.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 60)
    Donald G. Abbott (1944) (Adm). Course catalogue delayed (includes photo).
  - Tufts Weekly, 1967 April 14; UP056.001.060.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 15 Megabytes (Box 60)
    [Admissions] Forum on policy. p. 9.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1967 April 21; UP056.001.060.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 60)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1967 April 28; UP056.001.060.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 60)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1967 May 05; UP056.001.060.00029; 1 Digital Object(s); 14 Megabytes (Box 60)
    Academic Honors; pp.1,3. Freeland Abbott (faculty). Appointed to Board of the Experimental College (includes photo).
  - Tufts Weekly, 1967 May 12; UP056.001.060.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 60)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1967 September 18; UP056.001.061.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 61)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1967 September 22; UP056.001.061.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 61)
    Freeland K. Abbott, Injured in auto accident, p. 4.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1967 September 29; UP056.001.061.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 20 Megabytes (Box 61)
    Adminstration 1967-68. Changes in,
  - Tufts Weekly, 1967 October 06; UP056.001.061.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 61)
    Adminstration 1967. Development Office (includes photo of Frank Tredenick).
  - Tufts Weekly, 1967 October 20; UP056.001.061.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 22 Megabytes (Box 61)
    Adminstration 1967. Denies relevance of "in low parentis" at Tufts.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1967 October 27; UP056.001.061.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 27 Megabytes (Box 61)
    [Afro-American Society] Activities, p. 1.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1967 November 03; UP056.001.061.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 27 Megabytes (Box 61)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1967 November 10; UP056.001.061.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 26 Megabytes (Box 61)
    [Afro-American Society] Activities, p. 10.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1967 November 17; UP056.001.061.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 27 Megabytes (Box 61)
    Academic Honors; Awards; pp.1,9; [American association of university professors] Views student rights
  - Tufts Weekly, 1967 December 01; UP056.001.061.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 26 Megabytes (Box 61)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1967 December 08; UP056.001.061.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 25 Megabytes (Box 61)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1967 December 15; UP056.001.061.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 19 Megabytes (Box 61)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1968 January 12; UP056.001.061.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 21 Megabytes (Box 61)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1968 February 09; UP056.001.061.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 27 Megabytes (Box 61)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1968 February 16; UP056.001.061.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 28 Megabytes (Box 61)
    [Alpha Epsilon Pi] Awarded President's Trophy [incl. photo].
  - Tufts Weekly, 1968 February 23; UP056.001.061.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 20 Megabytes (Box 61)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1968 March 01; UP056.001.061.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 21 Megabytes (Box 61)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1968 March 08; UP056.001.061.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 23 Megabytes (Box 61)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1968 March 15; UP056.001.061.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 20 Megabytes (Box 61)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1968 March 22; UP056.001.061.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 20 Megabytes (Box 61)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1968 April 01; UP056.001.061.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 23 Megabytes (Box 61)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1968 April 12; UP056.001.061.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 19 Megabytes (Box 61)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1968 April 19; UP056.001.061.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 61)
    [Admissions] Aid officers point to lack of funds (incl. photo of Dean John C. Palmer). p. 3.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1968 April 26; UP056.001.061.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 18 Megabytes (Box 61)
    [Admissions] Aid officers point to lack of funds (incl. photo of Dean John C. Palmer). pp. 1, 3.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1968 May 03; UP056.001.061.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 61)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1968 May 10; UP056.001.061.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 26 Megabytes (Box 61)
    [Afro-American Society] Activities, p. 3.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1968 September 09; UP056.001.062.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 62)
    Administration 1968. Changes in,
  - Tufts Weekly, 1968 September 13; UP056.001.062.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 9 Megabytes (Box 62)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1968 September 20; UP056.001.062.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 62)
    Academic Calendar, 1968-69, New University Calendar, p. 3.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1968 October 04; UP056.001.062.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 62)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1968 October 11; UP056.001.062.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 62)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1968 October 18; UP056.001.062.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 62)
    Academic Ceremonies 1968. Experimental degree sought by Experimental College.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1968 October 25; UP056.001.062.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 62)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1968 November 01; UP056.001.062.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 62)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1968 November 08; UP056.001.062.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 22 Megabytes (Box 62)
    [Adler, Richard] Zeroxography. P. 3.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1968 November 15; UP056.001.062.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 23 Megabytes (Box 62)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1968 November 22; UP056.001.062.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 28 Megabytes (Box 62)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1968 December 06; UP056.001.062.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 22 Megabytes (Box 62)
- Tufts Weekly, 1902 -- 1917; UP056.002.GB (Box 1)
  microfilm reel, not yet processed. Former barcode 39090015515931g